// src/questions.js

export const questionBank = [
    // Anime Questions
    {
        questionText: 'In "Jujutsu Kaisen", what is the name of Satoru Gojo\'s Domain Expansion?',
        answerOptions: [
            { answerText: 'Infinite Void', isCorrect: true },
            { answerText: 'Malevolent Shrine', isCorrect: false },
            { answerText: 'Self-Embodiment of Perfection', isCorrect: false },
            { answerText: 'Chimera Shadow Garden', isCorrect: false },
        ],
    },
    {
        questionText: 'What is the primary goal of the scouts in "Attack on Titan"?',
        answerOptions: [
            { answerText: 'To build bigger walls', isCorrect: false },
            { answerText: 'To reclaim territory from Titans', isCorrect: true },
            { answerText: 'To find a new continent', isCorrect: false },
            { answerText: 'To negotiate peace with the Titans', isCorrect: false },
        ],
    },
    {
        questionText: 'In "Demon Slayer", what is the name of the breathing style Tanjiro first learns?',
        answerOptions: [
            { answerText: 'Sun Breathing', isCorrect: false },
            { answerText: 'Flame Breathing', isCorrect: false },
            { answerText: 'Water Breathing', isCorrect: true },
            { answerText: 'Wind Breathing', isCorrect: false },
        ],
    },
    {
        questionText: 'In "My Hero Academia", what is Izuku Midoriya\'s Quirk?',
        answerOptions: [
            { answerText: 'Explosion', isCorrect: false },
            { answerText: 'One For All', isCorrect: true },
            { answerText: 'Half-Cold Half-Hot', isCorrect: false },
            { answerText: 'Zero Gravity', isCorrect: false },
        ],
    },
    {
        questionText: 'Who is known as the "Chainsaw Man" in the anime of the same name?',
        answerOptions: [
            { answerText: 'Aki Hayakawa', isCorrect: false },
            { answerText: 'Power', isCorrect: false },
            { answerText: 'Denji', isCorrect: true },
            { answerText: 'Makima', isCorrect: false },
        ],
    },
    // ... (We'll add 45 more questions here for a total of 50)
    { questionText: 'In "Naruto", what is Kakashi\'s signature jutsu?', answerOptions: [{ answerText: 'Rasengan', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'Chidori', isCorrect: true }, { answerText: 'Shadow Clone Jutsu', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'Fireball Jutsu', isCorrect: false }] },
    { questionText: 'What is the name of the pirate crew led by Monkey D. Luffy in "One Piece"?', answerOptions: [{ answerText: 'Heart Pirates', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'Kid Pirates', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'Straw Hat Pirates', isCorrect: true }, { answerText: 'Blackbeard Pirates', isCorrect: false }] },
    { questionText: 'In "Spy x Family", what is Anya\'s secret ability?', answerOptions: [{ answerText: 'Super strength', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'Telepathy', isCorrect: true }, { answerText: 'Invisibility', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'Time travel', isCorrect: false }] },
    { questionText: 'In "Death Note", what must you know about a person to kill them with the notebook?', answerOptions: [{ answerText: 'Their face and name', isCorrect: true }, { answerText: 'Their birthdate', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'Their address', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'Their greatest fear', isCorrect: false }] },
    { questionText: 'What is the name of the virtual reality MMORPG in "Sword Art Online"?', answerOptions: [{ answerText: 'Alfheim Online', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'Gun Gale Online', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'Aincrad', isCorrect: true }, { answerText: 'Underworld', isCorrect: false }] },
    { questionText: 'What is the main objective in "Haikyuu!!"?', answerOptions: [{ answerText: 'To win the national high school volleyball tournament', isCorrect: true }, { answerText: 'To become the best swimmer', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'To win a basketball championship', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'To be the best ping pong player', isCorrect: false }] },
    { questionText: 'Who is the "One-Punch Man"?', answerOptions: [{ answerText: 'Genos', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'Saitama', isCorrect: true }, { answerText: 'King', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'Blast', isCorrect: false }] },
    { questionText: 'In "Fullmetal Alchemist: Brotherhood", what is the law of equivalent exchange?', answerOptions: [{ answerText: 'To gain something, something of equal value must be lost', isCorrect: true }, { answerText: 'Magic can solve any problem', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'Friendship conquers all', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'Power is absolute', isCorrect: false }] },
    { questionText: 'In "Tokyo Ghoul", what are ghouls?', answerOptions: [{ answerText: 'Vampires that drink blood', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'Creatures that eat human flesh', isCorrect: true }, { answerText: 'Spirits that haunt buildings', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'Aliens from another planet', isCorrect: false }] },
    { questionText: 'What is the name of the main character in "Dr. Stone"?', answerOptions: [{ answerText: 'Taiju', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'Senku', isCorrect: true }, { answerText: 'Gen', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'Chrome', isCorrect: false }] },
    { questionText: 'In "The Promised Neverland", what is the dark secret of Grace Field House?', answerOptions: [{ answerText: 'It\'s a school for spies', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'The children are raised as food for demons', isCorrect: true }, { answerText: 'It\'s a government experiment', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'The caretaker is a witch', isCorrect: false }] },
    { questionText: 'What is the name of the flame-wielding hero in "Fire Force"?', answerOptions: [{ answerText: 'Arthur Boyle', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'Shinra Kusakabe', isCorrect: true }, { answerText: 'Akitaru Obi', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'Takehisa Hinawa', isCorrect: false }] },
    { questionText: 'In "Vinland Saga", what is Thorfinn\'s primary motivation in the first season?', answerOptions: [{ answerText: 'To find Vinland', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'To avenge his father\'s death', isCorrect: true }, { answerText: 'To become a king', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'To become a wealthy merchant', isCorrect: false }] },
    { questionText: 'What is the power system in "Hunter x Hunter"?', answerOptions: [{ answerText: 'Chakra', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'Nen', isCorrect: true }, { answerText: 'Alchemy', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'Quirks', isCorrect: false }] },
    { questionText: 'In "Steins;Gate", what household appliance is part of the time machine?', answerOptions: [{ answerText: 'A toaster', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'A microwave', isCorrect: true }, { answerText: 'A washing machine', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'A refrigerator', isCorrect: false }] },
    { questionText: 'What is the goal of the game in "Mob Psycho 100"?', answerOptions: [{ answerText: 'To become the strongest esper', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'To live a normal life and control his powers', isCorrect: true }, { answerText: 'To conquer the world', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'To find his lost brother', isCorrect: false }] },
    { questionText: 'In "Re:Zero", what is Subaru Natsuki\'s ability?', answerOptions: [{ answerText: 'Super strength', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'Return by Death', isCorrect: true }, { answerText: 'Mind reading', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'Invisibility', isCorrect: false }] },
    { questionText: 'In "Bleach", what are the soul reapers called?', answerOptions: [{ answerText: 'Ninja', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'Shinigami', isCorrect: true }, { answerText: 'Hollows', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'Quincies', isCorrect: false }] },
    { questionText: 'What is the name of the virtual reality game in "Overlord"?', answerOptions: [{ answerText: 'Yggdrasil', isCorrect: true }, { answerText: 'Elder Tales', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'The World', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'Sword Art Online', isCorrect: false }] },
    { questionText: 'In "Code Geass", what is the power that Lelouch receives?', answerOptions: [{ answerText: 'The ability to stop time', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'The power of absolute obedience', isCorrect: true }, { answerText: 'The ability to read minds', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'The ability to fly', isCorrect: false }] },

    // Gaming Questions
    {
        questionText: 'In "Valorant", which agent has the ultimate ability "Tour De Force"?',
        answerOptions: [
            { answerText: 'Jett', isCorrect: false },
            { answerText: 'Sova', isCorrect: false },
            { answerText: 'Reyna', isCorrect: false },
            { answerText: 'Chamber', isCorrect: true },
        ],
    },
    {
        questionText: 'Which of these is NOT an element you can control in "Genshin Impact"?',
        answerOptions: [
            { answerText: 'Pyro (Fire)', isCorrect: false },
            { answerText: 'Chrono (Time)', isCorrect: true },
            { answerText: 'Anemo (Wind)', isCorrect: false },
            { answerText: 'Geo (Earth)', isCorrect: false },
        ],
    },
    {
        questionText: 'In "Fortnite", what is the name of the in-game currency?',
        answerOptions: [
            { answerText: 'Gems', isCorrect: false },
            { answerText: 'V-Bucks', isCorrect: true },
            { answerText: 'Fort-Coins', isCorrect: false },
            { answerText: 'Battle Bux', isCorrect: false },
        ],
    },
    {
        questionText: 'What is the main objective of the "Impostor" in the game "Among Us"?',
        answerOptions: [
            { answerText: 'To complete all tasks first', isCorrect: false },
            { answerText: 'To sabotage the ship and eliminate the crewmates', isCorrect: true },
            { answerText: 'To vote out the wrong person', isCorrect: false },
            { answerText: 'To fix the communications array', isCorrect: false },
        ],
    },
    {
        questionText: 'What is the name of the final boss in "Minecraft"?',
        answerOptions: [
            { answerText: 'The Wither', isCorrect: false },
            { answerText: 'The Ender Dragon', isCorrect: true },
            { answerText: 'Herobrine', isCorrect: false },
            { answerText: 'The Warden', isCorrect: false },
        ],
    },
    {
        questionText: 'In "Elden Ring", players explore a world known as...',
        answerOptions: [
            { answerText: 'Lordran', isCorrect: false },
            { answerText: 'The Lands Between', isCorrect: true },
            { answerText: 'Yharnam', isCorrect: false },
            { answerText: 'Hyrule', isCorrect: false },
        ],
    },
    { questionText: 'In "Animal Crossing: New Horizons", who is the raccoon that manages the island\'s finances?', answerOptions: [{ answerText: 'Tom Nook', isCorrect: true }, { answerText: 'Isabelle', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'K.K. Slider', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'Blathers', isCorrect: false }] },
    { questionText: 'What role does "Mirage" play in "Apex Legends"?', answerOptions: [{ answerText: 'Healer', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'Holographic Trickster', isCorrect: true }, { answerText: 'Tank', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'Sniper', isCorrect: false }] },
    { questionText: 'In "League of Legends", what is the main objective?', answerOptions: [{ answerText: 'Get the most kills', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'Destroy the enemy\'s Nexus', isCorrect: true }, { answerText: 'Slay Baron Nashor 10 times', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'Control all the towers', isCorrect: false }] },
    { questionText: 'What is the name of the main character in the "The Legend of Zelda" series that the player controls?', answerOptions: [{ answerText: 'Zelda', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'Link', isCorrect: true }, { answerText: 'Ganon', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'Epona', isCorrect: false }] },
    { questionText: 'In "Stardew Valley", what is the name of the town you move to?', answerOptions: [{ answerText: 'Mineral Town', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'Pelican Town', isCorrect: true }, { answerText: 'Forget-Me-Not Valley', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'Olive Town', isCorrect: false }] },
    { questionText: 'What company developed the game "Cyberpunk 2077"?', answerOptions: [{ answerText: 'Bethesda', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'CD PROJEKT RED', isCorrect: true }, { answerText: 'Ubisoft', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'Rockstar Games', isCorrect: false }] },
    { questionText: 'In "Overwatch 2", which character is a cyborg ninja?', answerOptions: [{ answerText: 'Hanzo', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'Genji', isCorrect: true }, { answerText: 'Tracer', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'Winston', isCorrect: false }] },
    { questionText: 'What is the name of the protagonist in "The Witcher 3: Wild Hunt"?', answerOptions: [{ answerText: 'Jaskier', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'Geralt of Rivia', isCorrect: true }, { answerText: 'Eredin', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'Vesemir', isCorrect: false }] },
    { questionText: 'In "Red Dead Redemption 2", who is the main protagonist?', answerOptions: [{ answerText: 'John Marston', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'Arthur Morgan', isCorrect: true }, { answerText: 'Dutch van der Linde', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'Micah Bell', isCorrect: false }] },
    { questionText: 'What type of game is "Hades"?', answerOptions: [{ answerText: 'A first-person shooter', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'A roguelike dungeon crawler', isCorrect: true }, { answerText: 'A racing game', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'A life simulation game', isCorrect: false }] },
    { questionText: 'In the "Pokémon" series, which of these is a starter Pokémon from the Kanto region?', answerOptions: [{ answerText: 'Totodile', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'Bulbasaur', isCorrect: true }, { answerText: 'Treecko', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'Scorbunny', isCorrect: false }] },
    { questionText: 'What is the primary goal in the game "Fall Guys"?', answerOptions: [{ answerText: 'To solve puzzles', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'To be the last one standing in a series of mini-games', isCorrect: true }, { answerText: 'To build a base', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'To defeat a final boss', isCorrect: false }] },
    { questionText: 'In "God of War" (2018), what is Kratos\'s son\'s name?', answerOptions: [{ answerText: 'Zeus', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'Atreus', isCorrect: true }, { answerText: 'Mimir', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'Baldur', isCorrect: false }] },
    { questionText: 'What is the name of the battle royale island in "Call of Duty: Warzone"?', answerOptions: [{ answerText: 'Erangel', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'Verdansk/Caldera/Al Mazrah (all are valid)', isCorrect:true}, { answerText: 'Kings Canyon', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'The Island', isCorrect: false }] },
    { questionText: 'Which game features characters like "Steve" and "Alex" and involves building with blocks?', answerOptions: [{ answerText: 'Terraria', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'Minecraft', isCorrect: true }, { answerText: 'Roblox', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'Stardew Valley', isCorrect: false }] },
    { questionText: 'What is the name of the AI companion in the "Halo" series?', answerOptions: [{ answerText: 'Siri', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'Cortana', isCorrect: true }, { answerText: 'Alexa', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'GLaDOS', isCorrect: false }] },
    { questionText: 'In "Street Fighter", what is Ryu\'s signature move?', answerOptions: [{ answerText: 'Spinning Bird Kick', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'Hadouken', isCorrect: true }, { answerText: 'Shoryuken', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'Tatsumaki Senpukyaku', isCorrect: false }] },
    { questionText: 'What is the setting of "Ghost of Tsushima"?', answerOptions: [{ answerText: 'Feudal Japan', isCorrect: true }, { answerText: 'Ancient Greece', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'Viking-era Norway', isCorrect: false }, { answerText: 'The American Wild West', isCorrect: false }] },
];